<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2023-07-12T07:25:18+00:00</updated><id>https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">ISC22 获奖 ISC22 Award Winning</title><link href="https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/blog/2022/ISC22/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ISC22 获奖 ISC22 Award Winning"/><published>2022-06-03T10:18:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-06-03T10:18:00+00:00</updated><id>https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/blog/2022/ISC22</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/blog/2022/ISC22/"><![CDATA[<p>北京时间6月1日晚，2022年ISC国际超级计算机竞赛总决赛结果在德国汉堡举行的ISC22国际超算大会上公布，我校学生超算队在线上赛道获得季军，清华大学代表队与中山大学代表队分获冠亚军。这是我校学生超算队首次亮相ISC国际超算竞赛。</p> <p>On the evening of June 1, Beijing time, the results of the 2022 ISC International Supercomputing Competition Grand Final were announced at the ISC22 International Supercomputing Conference held in Hamburg, Germany, and our student supercomputing team won the third place in the online track, while the team from Tsinghua University and the team from Sun Yat-sen University won the first and second place. This is the first appearance of our student supercomputing team in ISC International Supercomputing Competition.</p> <p>ISC国际超算大会由国际高性能计算指导委员会和国际超算组织主办，是世界上历史最悠久、欧洲顶级的面向国际高性能计算社区的会议和网络活动，而作为会议的重要组成部分，ISC超算竞赛是超级计算机领域的顶级赛事之一，每年举办一次，与中国ASC、美国SC并称为世界三大超算赛事。</p> <p>The ISC International Supercomputing Conference, organized by the International Steering Committee for High Performance Computing and the International Supercomputing Organization, is the world’s oldest and top European conference and networking event for the international high performance computing community, and as an important part of the conference, the ISC Supercomputing Competition is one of the top events in the supercomputing field, held once a year, and is known as one of the world’s top three supercomputing The ISC Supercomputing Competition is one of the top supercomputing events in the field.</p> <p>我校在去年APAC HPC-AI竞赛中夺冠后受邀参加今年的ISC线上竞赛，并与包括清华大学、苏黎世联邦理工学院、南洋理工大学、佐治亚理工学院等来自全球10个国家17支入围团队同台竞技。受新冠疫情影响，本次总决赛分线上与线下两个赛道举行，线上赛有12支队伍参加，线下赛有5支队伍参加，线上竞赛要求各参赛队伍在3月14日至5月20日期间，通过使用美国匹兹堡超级计算中心集群（Bridges-2）、加拿大多伦多大学超算集群（Niagara）和国际高性能计算与人工智能咨询委员会高性能中心集群（Thor）完成赛题的运行与优化。本次比赛的赛题包括开源计算化学软件NWChem、下一代全球数值天气预报和气候建模系统ICON、高阶有限差分湍流求解器Xcompact3d及其性能优化编程挑战Coding Challenge，同时还设置了社交媒体展示、采访答辩等环节。南科大学生超算团队成员在克服了各类技术问题、跨国沟通交流等困难后，凭借着高效的队内配合及以往比赛中积累的经验和策略，最终获得了本次大赛的季军。</p> <p>After winning the APAC HPC-AI competition last year, our university was invited to participate in this year’s ISC online competition and compete with 17 finalist teams from 10 countries around the world, including Tsinghua University, ETH Zurich, Nanyang Technological University, and Georgia Institute of Technology. Affected by the new crown epidemic, the finals were held in two tracks, online and offline, with 12 teams participating in the online competition and 5 teams in the offline competition. The online competition required teams to compete between March 14 and May 20 by using the Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center cluster (Bridges-2) in the United States, the University of Toronto supercomputing cluster (Niagara) in Canada, and the International High Performance Computing and Artificial Intelligence Advisory Committee High Performance Center Cluster (Thor) to run and optimize the competition questions. The competition questions included the open source computational chemistry software NWChem, the next-generation global numerical weather forecasting and climate modeling system ICON, the high-order finite-difference turbulence solver Xcompact3d and its performance-optimized programming challenge Coding Challenge, as well as social media presentations and interviews and defense sessions. After overcoming various technical problems, cross-country communication and other difficulties, the members of the SUSTech student supercomputing team won the third place in the competition with their efficient teamwork and the experience and strategies accumulated in previous competitions.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E6%80%BB%E5%86%B3%E8%B5%9B%E5%8F%82%E8%B5%9B%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E6%80%BB%E5%86%B3%E8%B5%9B%E5%8F%82%E8%B5%9B%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E6%80%BB%E5%86%B3%E8%B5%9B%E5%8F%82%E8%B5%9B%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E6%80%BB%E5%86%B3%E8%B5%9B%E5%8F%82%E8%B5%9B%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E6%80%BB%E5%86%B3%E8%B5%9B%E6%95%99%E7%BB%83%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E6%80%BB%E5%86%B3%E8%B5%9B%E6%95%99%E7%BB%83%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E6%80%BB%E5%86%B3%E8%B5%9B%E6%95%99%E7%BB%83%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E6%80%BB%E5%86%B3%E8%B5%9B%E6%95%99%E7%BB%83%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> ISC22总决赛参赛团队及教练团队 ISC22 Finals Team and Coaching Team </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E8%B6%85%E7%AE%97%E7%AB%9E%E8%B5%9B%E7%BD%91%E7%AB%99%E6%88%AA%E5%9B%BE-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E8%B6%85%E7%AE%97%E7%AB%9E%E8%B5%9B%E7%BD%91%E7%AB%99%E6%88%AA%E5%9B%BE-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E8%B6%85%E7%AE%97%E7%AB%9E%E8%B5%9B%E7%BD%91%E7%AB%99%E6%88%AA%E5%9B%BE-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/ISC22%E8%B6%85%E7%AE%97%E7%AB%9E%E8%B5%9B%E7%BD%91%E7%AB%99%E6%88%AA%E5%9B%BE.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> ISC22超算竞赛网站截图 Screenshot of ISC22 Supercomputing Competition website </div> <p>南方科技大学超算队作为新近出现的参赛队伍，在比赛中展现了不俗的实力，已在包括ASC、SC SCC、APAC HPC-AI等多项国际超算大赛中取得优异战绩。此次ISC竞赛由前南科大超算队队长南科大超算俱乐部发起人赵佳华（现在意大利帕多瓦大学攻读硕士学位）指导，计算机科学与工程系助理教授李卓钊老师、科学与工程计算中心主任工程师范靖博士、计算机科学与工程系18级本科生顾同舟提供技术协助，学生超算队队长由生物系18级本科生张懿麒担任，队员由计算机科学与工程系20级郑英炜，深港微电子学院18级袁通、樊青远，力学与航空航天工程系18级冀潇以及统计与数据科学系18级骆镒玲共5位本科同学组成。此次比赛后，南科大学生超算队成为国内为数不多的完整参加三大国际超算竞赛并获荣誉的高校团队（ASC19应用创新奖和一等奖，ASC 20-21一等奖，SC21最高性能奖和季军，ISC22季军）。</p> <p>The SUSTech supercomputing team, as a newly emerged team, has shown remarkable strength in the competition and has already achieved excellent results in many international supercomputing competitions including ASC, SC SCC, and APAC HPC-AI. The ISC competition was directed by former SUSTech supercomputing team leader Jiahua Zhao, the initiator of the SUSTech Supercomputing Club (now pursuing a master’s degree at the University of Padova, Italy), with technical assistance from Mr. Zhuozhao Li, Assistant Professor of the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Dr. Jing Fan, Director Engineer of the Center for Scientific and Engineering Computing, and Tongzhou Gu, an ‘18 undergraduate student of the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, and the student supercomputing team captained by Biology ‘18 The team leader was Zhang Yiqi, an undergraduate student from the Department of Biology, Grade 18, and the team members were Zheng Yingwei, Grade 20, Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Yuan Tong and Fan Qingyuan, Grade 18, Department of Microelectronics, Shenzhen and Hong Kong, Ji Xiao, Grade 18, Department of Mechanics and Aerospace Engineering, and Luo Yiling, Grade 18, Department of Statistics and Data Science, a total of five undergraduate students. After this competition, the SUSTech Student Supercomputing Team became one of the few university teams in China that participated in all three major international supercomputing competitions and won honors (ASC19 Application Innovation Award and First Prize, ASC 20-21 First Prize, SC21 Top Performance Award and Third Prize, ISC22 Third Prize).</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/%E5%8D%97%E7%A7%91%E5%A4%A7%E5%8F%82%E8%B5%9B%E6%88%90%E5%91%98%E7%BA%BF%E4%B8%8A%E5%90%88%E7%85%A7-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/%E5%8D%97%E7%A7%91%E5%A4%A7%E5%8F%82%E8%B5%9B%E6%88%90%E5%91%98%E7%BA%BF%E4%B8%8A%E5%90%88%E7%85%A7-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/%E5%8D%97%E7%A7%91%E5%A4%A7%E5%8F%82%E8%B5%9B%E6%88%90%E5%91%98%E7%BA%BF%E4%B8%8A%E5%90%88%E7%85%A7-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/blogs/2022-06-03-ISC22/%E5%8D%97%E7%A7%91%E5%A4%A7%E5%8F%82%E8%B5%9B%E6%88%90%E5%91%98%E7%BA%BF%E4%B8%8A%E5%90%88%E7%85%A7.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> 南科大参赛成员线上合照 Group photo of the participating members of SUSTech online </div> <p>在参赛和备赛阶段，南科大科学与工程计算中心为学生提供了丰富的计算资源，展现了南科大计算平台在人才培养方面的强大优势。</p> <p>During the competition and preparation phase, SUSTech’s Scientific and Engineering Computing Center provided students with abundant computing resources, demonstrating the strong advantages of SUSTech’s computing platform in talent training.</p> <p><a href="https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/G-BAtbxU_34VV_q01J_2eg">原文链接</a></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="achievement"/><category term="competition"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[南科大学生超算队首获ISC22国际超算竞赛总决赛季军 SUSTech Student Supercomputing Team Wins First Third Place in ISC22 International Supercomputing Competition Finals]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SC21 SCC 获奖 SC21 SCC Award Winning</title><link href="https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/blog/2021/SC21/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SC21 SCC 获奖 SC21 SCC Award Winning"/><published>2021-11-22T12:25:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-11-22T12:25:00+00:00</updated><id>https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/blog/2021/SC21</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tonanguyxiro.github.io/blog/2021/SC21/"><![CDATA[<p>近日，国际高性能计算及人工智能咨询委员会和世界大学生超算大赛（SCC）组委会于2021年度国际超算大会（SC21）期间先后宣布了第4届APAC HPC-AI竞赛和SC21 SCC两场赛事的成绩。南方科技大学荣获本届APAC HPC-AI竞赛第一名暨大赛总冠军和AI特别奖。同时，在SC21 SCC中取得了最高性能奖，总分排在清华大学和上海科技大学之后，位列第三。此外，由于在APAC HPC-AI竞赛中的优异表现，南科大超算队将获得明年在德国举行的ISC22国际大学生超算竞赛的一个保留席位。</p> <p>Recently, the International High Performance Computing and Artificial Intelligence Advisory Committee and the World Student Supercomputing Competition (SCC) Organizing Committee announced the results of the 4th APAC HPC-AI Competition and the SC21 SCC during the 2021 International Supercomputing Conference (SC21). SUSTech was awarded the first place of this year’s APAC HPC-AI competition and the overall champion of the competition and the AI Special Award. Meanwhile, it achieved the highest performance award in SC21 SCC and ranked third in the total score after Tsinghua University and Shanghai University of Science and Technology. In addition, due to its excellent performance in the APAC HPC-AI competition, the SUSTech supercomputing team will be awarded a reserved seat in the ISC22 International Student Supercomputing Competition to be held in Germany next year.</p> <p>自南科大超算俱乐部组建以来，南科大学生超算队已在包括ASC、APAC HPC-AI、SC SCC等多项国际大赛中取得优异战绩，此次两项竞赛中取得的成绩均为南科大历史最好成绩。</p> <p>Since the formation of the SUSTech Supercomputing Club, the SUSTech Student Supercomputing Team has achieved excellent results in many international competitions, including ASC, APAC HPC-AI and SC SCC, and the results achieved in both competitions are the best results in the history of SUSTech.</p> <p>全球超级计算大会（Supercomputing Conference，简称SC）是国际超算领域的顶级会议，国际影响力巨大。作为会议的重要组成部分，SCC（Student Cluster Competition）比赛是世界大学生超算顶级赛事之一，每年举办一次，吸引了世界各国和地区众多高校的目光。</p> <p>The Supercomputing Conference (SC) is the top international conference in supercomputing with great international influence. As an important part of the conference, SCC (Student Cluster Competition) is one of the top supercomputing competitions for university students in the world, which is held once a year and attracts the attention of many universities in different countries and regions around the world.</p> <p>受疫情影响，本次SCC竞赛在线上举办。为适应线上比赛的特殊情况，竞赛组委会今年设计了新的比赛规则，为各参赛队提供了一套固定配置的Oracle云集群和Azure云上的1500美元预算用于搭建个性化集群。各参赛队需用这两套集群完成特定赛题。此外，本次比赛还要求各队分析两套云集群的特点和赛题的性能特征，合理规划预算和计算时间，充分发挥出各集群的优势和性能，尽可能提高基准性能分数并高效地求解出一系列科学问题。</p> <p>Affected by the epidemic, this SCC competition was held online. In order to adapt to the special situation of online competition, the competition organizing committee designed new competition rules this year, providing teams with a fixed configuration of Oracle Cloud Cluster and a budget of $1500 on Azure Cloud for building personalized clusters. Teams were required to use these two clusters to complete specific competition questions. In addition, the competition required teams to analyze the characteristics of the two cloud clusters and the performance characteristics of the problem, plan their budgets and computation times to fully exploit the strengths and performance of each cluster, improve their benchmark performance scores and solve a series of scientific problems as efficiently as possible.</p> <p>今年的赛题包括性能基准测试程序LINPACK、HPCG、IO500，多尺度心脏模拟 Cardioid，量子材料模拟Quantum ESPRESSO，SC20论文复现题“大规模贝叶斯网络并行学习框架ramBLe”，同时还设置了海报设计展示、采访答辩等环节。</p> <p>This year’s problems include performance benchmarking programs LINPACK, HPCG, IO500, multi-scale heart simulation Cardioid, quantum material simulation Quantum ESPRESSO, SC20 paper reproduction problem “large-scale Bayesian network parallel learning framework ramBLe”, as well as There were also poster design presentation and interview defense sessions.</p> <p>南科大团队成员在克服了各类技术问题，远程比赛的时差，以及46小时连续比赛的疲劳等困难后，凭借着高效的队内沟通与配合，各队员强大的技战术实力与冷静的临场判断，以及在数次比赛中积累的经验和策略，获得了大赛LINPACK基准测试最高性能奖，同时取得了HPCG基准测试排名第一，多尺度心脏模拟 Cardioid赛题得分排名第二，SC20论文复现题得分排名第二，综合得分排名第三的好成绩。</p> <p>After overcoming various technical problems, the time difference of remote competition, and the fatigue of 46 hours of continuous competition, the team members of SUSTech won the highest performance award of LINPACK benchmark test and the first place of HPCG benchmark test with their efficient team communication and cooperation, strong technical and tactical strength and calm judgment of each team member, as well as the experience and strategies accumulated in several competitions. The team also won the first place in the HPCG benchmark test, the second place in the multi-scale cardiac simulation Cardioid question, the second place in the SC20 paper reproduction question, and the third place in the overall score.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2021-11-22-SC21/%E6%AF%94%E8%B5%9B%E7%BA%BF%E4%B8%8A%E9%A2%81%E5%A5%96%E6%88%AA%E5%9B%BE-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2021-11-22-SC21/%E6%AF%94%E8%B5%9B%E7%BA%BF%E4%B8%8A%E9%A2%81%E5%A5%96%E6%88%AA%E5%9B%BE-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2021-11-22-SC21/%E6%AF%94%E8%B5%9B%E7%BA%BF%E4%B8%8A%E9%A2%81%E5%A5%96%E6%88%AA%E5%9B%BE-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/blogs/2021-11-22-SC21/%E6%AF%94%E8%B5%9B%E7%BA%BF%E4%B8%8A%E9%A2%81%E5%A5%96%E6%88%AA%E5%9B%BE.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" data-zoomable="" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> 比赛线上颁奖截图 Screenshot of the competition online award </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2021-11-22-SC21/%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F%E6%88%90%E5%91%98-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2021-11-22-SC21/%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F%E6%88%90%E5%91%98-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/blogs/2021-11-22-SC21/%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F%E6%88%90%E5%91%98-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/blogs/2021-11-22-SC21/%E5%9B%A2%E9%98%9F%E6%88%90%E5%91%98.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" data-zoomable="" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> 团队成员 Team Members </div> <p>SC21 SCC赛事参赛队队长由计算机科学与工程系18级本科生顾同舟担任，队员由计算机科学与工程系18级许博添、20级郑英炜，深港微电子学院18级袁通，生物系18级张懿麒以及还未分专业的20级王炳臻共5位本科同学组成。</p> <p>The SC21 SCC team was led by Gu Tongzhou, a Grade 18 undergraduate student from the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, with five undergraduate students, including Xu Botian, Grade 18, and Zheng Yingwei, Grade 20 from the Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Yuan Tong, Grade 18 from the Shenzhen-Hong Kong Institute of Microelectronics, Zhang Yiqi, Grade 18 from the Department of Biology, and Wang Bingzhen, Grade 20, who has not yet been assigned a major.</p> <p>比赛准备期间，南科大科学与工程计算中心与旗下的学生超算俱乐部在比赛准备期间全程提供了丰富的计算资源和技术指导，展现了南科大在超算平台和计算资源方面的强大优势。</p> <p>During the preparation of the competition, SUSTech’s Scientific and Engineering Computing Center and its Student Supercomputing Club provided abundant computing resources and technical guidance throughout the preparation of the competition, demonstrating SUSTech’s strong advantages in supercomputing platforms and computing resources.</p> <p>2022年，南科大学生超算团队将继续积极准备和参加ISC22、ASC22等重大国际赛事，同时将继续与校内超算用户开展合作，培养新一代的南科大超算人才。</p> <p>In 2022, the SUSTech Student Supercomputing Team will continue to actively prepare for and participate in major international events such as ISC22 and ASC22, and will continue to cooperate with on-campus supercomputing users to cultivate a new generation of SUSTech supercomputing talents.</p> <p><a href="https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/5KUCVYio-WS_9FWSII2lAg">原文链接 Origin</a></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="achievement"/><category term="competition"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[南方科技大学超算队在SC21 SCC中取得了最高性能奖 SUSTech Supercomputing Team Achieves Top Performance Award in SC21 SCC]]></summary></entry></feed>